onlinetvplayer.com 2018-05-11

# OnlineTVPlayer.com Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |    
---|---|---  
|  |   |    
---|---|---  

#### OnlineTVPlayer.com

has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the OnlineTVPlayer.com network of sites.   

#### Our Privacy Guarantee 

We will never sell, rent or share any of your personal information with a third-party without your express prior permission. For customers, this means that the only people who will ever access your address and contact information are us and our credit card processor.   

#### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We may also use cookies to assist in the ordering and sales process.   

#### Advertisers 

We use an outside advertising company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Some anonymous demographic data is shared with the advertising companies on an aggregate basis. 

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.   

#### Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. OnlineTVPlayer.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.   

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.   

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please [contact us](http://www.onlinetvplayer.com/contact/) .   
|
